Shweta Shashikant Shinde

♥ Katraj, Pune

in Indiawww.linkedin.com/in/shweta-shinde-1461641

Indian

Female

Profile

Experience and motivational Associate with 3.5 years of experience in helping the team and steering business operations for maximum productivity and portability. Possessing ability to identify the issues in the operations and the methods to resolve them. Quick learner with excellent Data Organizational skills.

Education

SSC, Vishakarma Vidalaya (10) Pune, India

HSC, Garvare College Pune, India

BCOM, Yashwantrao Chavan Nashik, India

Awards

Spot Recognition Award

Courses

Tally ERP.9, Soham Institution Pune, India

Professional Business Accountant, Soham Pune, India

Certificates

- MS-CIT
- Typing Speed 25 30 WPM

Languages

English

Marathi

Hindi



Professional Experience

Customer Support (Finance), Infotech Software Pvt. Ltd 04/2022 - 10/2022 | Pune, India Create Purchase Order, Goods Received Note (GRN), Follow-up with customer for payment, Prepare Delivery Challan, Tax Invoice, daily basic transactions like Petty cash book, cash transactions

Sr. Associate in Capital Market (Investment

Banking), Atos Syntel

01/2020 – 03/2022 | Pune, India

Asset Servicing, Custodian Activities, Reconcile, Accounting processing

Processing various monetary transactions as per the instructions.

OMP, MT103 - Foreign, MT202, Checks, EM and VMW, Fed wire.

Accountant,

Oasis Institute of Health Science and Management 05/2019 - 12/2019 | Pune, India Accountant

Cash and Reconciliation

Accounting, Nilesh Enterprises 05/2018 - 04/2019 | Pune, India Client Relation, Accounting, Presentation Skills.

Post: Senior associate

Name of Company: SS&C (DST Services Ltd) Process: Asset Servicing Estate valuation Duration of Service:

Job Responsibility:

- Working on DOD valuation and stock transfer in estate valuation process.
- Responsible for checking death certificate, grant of probates and other dealing related documents.
- Transferring deceased client's estate to legal executors.
- Dealing of estate as per executor's instructions like reinvesting, selling & accumulation of funds.
- Mentoring new joiners and providing feedback and assisting on gueries.
- Allocating work among the team members.
- Being involved in process improvement practice and calls with the clients for business

transition over the phone.

Declaration

To work in a creative and challenging environment where I would constantly upgrade my knowledge and skills.

Interpersonal Skills, Quick learner with excellent Data Organizational skills.

Shweta Shinde Pune